first FDA submission for the therapeutic use of an antibody oligoconjugate. That FDA submission
is for accelerated approval in the DMD44, Saxon 44, skipping using dystrophin as a surrogate
biomarker. We previously received FDA breakthrough therapy designation for this. The submission
package is based on the outstanding data that we had in the Explore 44 study as well as long-term
follow-up. And we expect the first launch here in the first half of 27 with the ongoing phase
studies ongoing. We have multiple follow-on programs now targeting additional exons that
we'll be bringing forward as well. So we're quite excited to leverage this technology to take on
DMD across multiple areas.
And then with respect to the Delbrax data, we read out in the quarter as well that the phase 1-2
study at the target dose that we are taking into phase 3 studies met its primary and key secondary
biomarker endpoints. So as a reminder, this is a study that looked at KHDC1L and creatine
kinase reductions in the plasma. KHDC1L is a protein that's downstream. It's a protein that's
believed to be regulated by Dux4, Dux4 being the gene that's impacted in FSHD. And so having
these plasma biomarkers indicates that we have strong target engagement and muscle damage
reduction as indicated by the statistically significant creatine kinase reductions that we
saw. Our base case remains a submission in 2028. But based on the data that we've seen in the
biomarkers and ongoing work we're currently conducting to hopefully correlate the
biomarkers to Dux4 as well as clinical improvements in these patients. We plan to engage FDA and other
regulatory authorities in the coming months. And then we'll ultimately provide an update if those
regulatory authorities support our ability to file this medicine based on this data.
Now moving to slide 16. So we're on track for a busy second half. We already had four readouts in the
first half. In the second half, we expect we'll see some improvement. We're going to see some
improvement with pellicarsin, remibrutinib, and daldiserin readouts in the coming months. And then before the end of the year,
readouts for yonalimab, Revcedo, and HS, as well as additional readouts for phase two programs, QCZ484,